http://www.gicofindia.com/en/privacy-policy

×
Inviting Suggestions for Systemic Improvements in Government Organizations from Citizens
Central Vigilance Commission, at the outset of Vigilance Awareness Week, has launched a new initiative for citizens to suggest systemic improvements in Central Government Organisations.
These suggestions may be sent directly to the Central Vigilance Commission from 27.10.2020 to 14.11.2020 by email (coord1-cvc@nic.in) or telephone (011-24651632).
Citizens who wish to give suggestions for Systemic Improvements in General Insurance Corporation of India (GIC Re) can write to cord-suggestions@gicofindia.com. till 14.11.2020.
Scroll
Scroll
Select Language
CSR Corner|Retirees Corner|HR Corner|Public Disclosures|Public Grievances|Right to Information|AA+ |
Ranked 11th Among the top40 global reinsurancegroups by S&P Global Ratings
Page last updated on: 14/08/2012
Visitors : 8229589
Menu
HomeAbout Us
History in BriefVision / MissionCore ValuesCorporate Management
Board of Directors
Committees of CorporationExecutivesKey Persons / Key Managerial PersonsIndependent External MonitorRegulatory FrameworkSubsidiary Company
GIC Re South AfricaGIC Re India, Corporate Member LtdGIC Perestrakhovanie LLCMedia
News & AnnouncementEvents & VisitsPress Releases / Interviews / GIC Re in the NewsGalleryDownloadsTendersVideoContactArchivesBusiness
DomesticInternationalOverseas OfficesTraining / Risk Rating SystemsRatings / RankingsCorporate Login
Employee Self-Service (ESS) Portale-HelpdeskMailBoard Management SoftwareFinancials
Balance Sheet 2019-20Revenue AccountP & L AccountOver the YearsConsolidated Financial Statement 2019-20
BSP & LREVOutstanding Dues to CreditorsUK Branch Solvency & Financial Condition ReportCareersInvestors
Contact details of Registrar and Transfer Agent (RTA)Contact Us
LocationsBusiness Matrix
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Print
As a general rule, this website does not collect Personal Information about you when you visit the site. You can generally visit the site without revealing Personal Information, unless you choose to provide such information.
Site Visit Data
This website records your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes your server's address; the name of the top-level domain from which you access the Internet (for example, .gov, .com, .in, etc.); the type of browser you use; the date and time you access the site; the pages you have accessed and the documents downloaded and the previous Internet address from which you linked directly to the site.
We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider's logs.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of software code that an internet web site sends to your browser when you access information at that site. This site does not use cookies.
Email Management
Your email address will only be recorded if you choose to send a message. It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Your email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.
Collection of Personal Information
If you are asked for any other Personal Information you will be informed how it will be used if you choose to give it. If at any time you believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the webmaster through the contact us page.
Note: The use of the term "Personal Information" in this privacy statement refers to any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.
Ranked 11th Among the top 40 global reinsurancegroups by S&P Ranking
Quick Links
Invitation for Expression of Interest from Reinsurers/BrokersTender Result/ Cancellation: Notice Inviting E-Tender for Established, Reputed & Experienced Agency/ Contractors for providing drivers to GIC ReActuarial ApprenticesResponse to Queries for RFP for the Appointment of Contractor for Village AdoptionCorrigendum 01 - Change in Date of Opening of Technical Bids (IAD/2019-20/001)NOTICE TO ALL EMPLOYEES REGARDING RENEWAL OF GMC POLICY 2020
About UsHistory in BriefVision / MissionCore ValuesCorporate ManagementRegulatory FrameworkSubsidiary CompanyBusinessDomesticInternationalOverseas OfficesTraining / Risk Rating SystemsFinancialsBalance Sheet 2018-19Revenue AccountP & L AccountOver the YearsMediaNews & AnnouncementPress Releases / Interviews / GIC Re in the NewsGalleryDownloadsTendersVideoArchivesEvents & VisitsContact UsLocationsBusiness MatrixRatings / RankingsFAQsFeedback
CIN : L67200MH1972GOI016133 & IRDA Registration No: 112
Page last updated on: 14/08/2012
Visitors : 8229589
Terms & Conditions|Privacy Policy|Copyright Policy|Accessibility Statement|Hyperlinking Policy|Disclaimer|Help|
Application Development and Maintenance by Cyfuture
